You mean the Fus
Keep drinking
If it really is him
The Fu family can't miss out again
Did you know all along
I knew a little
About the Fus
Yeah
And about me
About how you might not be ordinary
I never felt I was ordinary
But I never thought
I'd have anything to do with the Fu Group
If they really are tied to
your past
You should decide whether to see them
I won't choose for you
Did you choose me back then because
you knew the Fus would come for me
I knew you might become powerful later on
But when I chose you
you were still standing in the corner of the wedding
and nobody took you seriously
I didn't choose you because of the Fus
I chose you because you are Fu Chenzhou
Not replying now
Yeah I can go over anytime
But I don't want to be pushed around by a text
You're not going to persuade me
You're not Gu Chengze
You don't need others to make decisions for you
I like the sound of that
Do you know this person